{
    "id": "e3efc090898a479aad792f942fb79f35",
    "title": "Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I will go to America after I ………………… finished my work here.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "am",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………… playing the piano when I entered the room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "was",
                "have been"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy …………………… become unconscious before the doctor came.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "was",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "........................................ you ever been to Tokyo?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Have",
                "Do",
                "Were"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This is what he ............................... not seem to understand.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "does",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They ................................. engaged in a heated argument.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "did",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You ................................... being considered for the job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "have",
                "am"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ................................. being shadowed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "am",
                "do"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The dinner .................................. being cooked.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "My car ........................................ in the garage.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "does",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}